Prakash S

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India



linkedin.com/in/prakashs25698



prakashs25698@gmail.com



8105762879

Summary

I'm a 21 year old student pursuing my bachelor's in computer science at presidency university. I like to explore the tech world, new gadgets, open source projects, frameworks and travel etc. I'm a strong supporter of open source. I write code for fun and develop applications to improvise my skills and also do freelancing.

Experience



Implementation Engineer

6d Technologies

Jan 2020 - Present (4 months +)



Strategic Marketing Intern

Relyon Softech Ltd.

May 2018 - Jul 2018 (3 months)

Education



Presidency University Bangalore

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science 2016 - 2020

Licenses & Certifications



Full Stack MERN Bootcamp - LearnCodeOnline.in

10816845033224101056



AI From the Data Center to the Edge - An Optimized Path Using Intel® Architecture - Intel

Corporation

13830080



Architecting with Google Compute Engine Specialization - Coursera

6ATL4238B5YR



Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4 - Coursera

3ULX9T4A2KEX

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • React.js • MERN Stack • Google Cloud Platform (GCP) • Linux • MySQL • PHP • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML5